Dusa Praharshnand

https://dusa-praharsh.netlify.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dusa-praharsh/

My Contact

✓ dusapraharsh123@gmail.com

💽 Hyderabad, India 500020

+91 9705783228
https://github.com/DusaPraharsh

Professional Summary

I'm a self-taught developer with almost 2 years of experience across multiple streams such as Front-end, Blockchain and Game development. I believe the skill sets I possess would help me acquire exposure, experience and sharpen my skills amidst your organization's work culture.

Education

Avanthi Degree and PG College - BSc Computer Science - September 2019 -- July 2022 80% Aggregate

Narayana Junior College - MPC - July 2017 -- July 2019 71% Aggregate

Work Experience

Travel | Exploring Technologies |

Crypto and NFT Trading

Internship as Unity / Blockchain Developer at Kanine Klans - October 2023 -- Current Unity | C# | Solidity

Solidity Developer at Vivin Software - April 2023 -- August 2023 Solidity | Hardhat | Git

Freelance Front-end Developer at Hostwire Systems - February 2023 -- April 2023 React | JSX

Computing Skills	Achievements	Projects
Javascript React Solidity Hardhat	1st in Eth For All Hackathon, Hyderabad, India Runner up at Web3 Conf India' 23, Goa, India	PayStream (Unofficial) Pay as you stream application Javascript React Solidity
Threejs Blender Unity C# Git Github		SupplyX (Unofficial) Application which integrates workflow of Manufacturers,
Interests Gaming Web Development		Retailers and Customers using Blockchain Javascript React Solidity